tech4learning.com 2016-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Tech4Learning

This document sets forth the Tech4Learning Online Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") for this Web site (the "Site"). If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use this Site.

For the Privacy Policy for Wixie, please visit the [Wixie Privacy Policy](https://static.wixie.com/privacy.php) page.

### Collection of personal information

As a visitor to this Site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. In connection with other activities, such as subscribing to the collaboration services offered on the Site or utilizing online software applications, Tech4Learning may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, Tech4Learning may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including ZIP code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and fax numbers, and other personal information.

When ordering products or services on the Site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. 

When you use the Site, Tech4Learning or third parties authorized by Tech4Learning may also collect certain technical and routing information about your computer to facilitate your use of the Site and its services. For example, we may log environmental variables, such as browser type, operating system, CPU speed, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer. We use these environmental variables to facilitate and track your use of the Site and its services. Tech4Learning also uses such environmental variables to measure traffic patterns on the Site. Without expressly informing you in each particular circumstance, we do not match such information with any of your personal information.

When you submit personal information to Tech4Learning through this Site, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which Tech4Learning and its affiliates and subsidiaries maintain offices, including, without limitation, the United States. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transferring, storage, and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted vendors of Tech4Learning. Such vendors are bound by contract not to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third parties. 

Tech4Learning has established relationships with various service providers whose services are available to you from this Site or from Web sites that are linked to this Site. Typically, these providers offer services that Tech4Learning customers might find useful, such as those that can be used in conjunction with Tech4Learning services and products. In order to use those services, you may be required to provide personal information to the providers. Unless expressly provided to the contrary, personal information that you provide while you are visiting a provider's Web site will be subject to the privacy policy posted on such site, and personal information that you provide while on this Site in conjunction with a provider's service will be subject to this Privacy Policy. You should be aware that our agreements with these service providers often provide that they will share with Tech4Learning personal information collected from you. In such instances, Tech4Learning may use this information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy.

### How your personal information is used

Tech4Learning collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. If you subscribe to a service or register a product, for example, the information is used to register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits that may be made available to registered users. As another example, if you enter a contest, information is collected to qualify the entry and contact you regarding the contest or prize awards. Your personal information is also used to keep you informed about product upgrades, special offers, and other products and services of Tech4Learning and selected third parties.

Tech4Learning may collect information about the use of the Site; such as the types of services used and how many users we receive daily. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually. Tech4Learning may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes.

### Your choices with respect to personal information

Tech4Learning recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on this Site. Except in the particular circumstances described in this Privacy Policy, Tech4Learning will also not provide your name to other companies or organizations without your consent.

There are other instances in which Tech4Learning may divulge your personal information. Tech4Learning may provide your personal information if necessary, in Tech4Learning's good faith judgment, to comply with laws or regulations of a governmental or regulatory body or in response to a valid subpoena, warrant, or order or to protect the rights of Tech4Learning or others.

### Protection of your personal information

The personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself as a user of Tech4Learning products or services or registering a Tech4Learning product is classified as Registration Information. Registration Information is protected in several ways. Access by you to your Registration Information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. In addition, your Registration Information resides on a secure server that only selected Tech4Learning personnel and contractors have access to via password. Tech4Learning encrypts your personal information and thereby strives to prevent unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is transmitted to Tech4Learning.

Personal information that you provide that does not constitute Registration Information also resides on a secure server and is accessible only to selected Tech4Learning personnel and contractors via password. Since this information is not accessible by you, you will not be asked to select a password in order to view or modify such information.

Please note that any information you post to a public bulletin board or chat room is available to all persons accessing that Site.

### Children

Except as noted in product specific privacy policies. Tech4Learning does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13 without first receiving verifiable parental consent we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

### Use of cookies

When you visit this Site, you can browse the Site and access important information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our Site, we use "cookies" to track your visit. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card, and enables Tech4Learning to record your passwords, purchases, and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. 

When you visit this Site, third parties may place cookies and web beacons on your computer in order to collect information. These third parties may be providing advertising services, social media services, or other services to Tech4Learning.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. (For some Web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.) For help managing cookies in your specific browser, consult the Help system that accompanies your browser.

### Privacy-related complaints

Tech4Learning takes its users' privacy concerns seriously. If you believe that Tech4Learning has not complied with this Online Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, you may write the Tech4Learning Privacy Officer at the address indicated above.

In your letter, please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that the Tech4Learning Online Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly.

Please note that if you provide Tech4Learning with inconsistent privacy preferences (for example, by indicating on one occasion that third parties may contact you with marketing offers and indicating on another occasion that they may not), Tech4Learning cannot guarantee that your most recent privacy preference will be honored.

Also, please note that Tech4Learning is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Tech4Learning Web sites to which this Site or any other Tech4Learning Web site may link. You should review the privacy policy of such sites before using the sites.

### Entities collecting personal information

Personal information on this Site is collected by Tech4Learning Incorporated. Tech4Learning's address is 10981 San Diego Mission Rd. Suite 120, San Diego, CA 92108, and its telephone number is 619-563-5348.

The Site contains links to other sites at which personal information is collected. In such instances, unless expressly provided to the contrary, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site.

### Changes in Privacy Policy

All "personal information" ("personal information" is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains) that we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. Tech4Learning reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion, and will provide notice of material changes on the home page of the Site. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, such changes by your continued use of the Site after such notice has been posted for thirty (30) days. Tech4Learning will not sell or lease your personal information except, if Tech4Learning (or a division or subsidiary) is acquired by or merged with, another entity, Tech4Learning may provide to such entity customer information that is related to that part of our business that was sold to or merged with the other entity without your consent.
